LINA LEKOVA

Full-stack web developer

github.com/lekova

Iina.lekova@gmail.com

google.com/+LinaLekova

(781) 609-8789

twitter.com/linalekova

I am self-motivated full stack web developer with background in software development as well as marketing and advertising. I am excited about learning new technologies and expanding my skill set. I love working in a team where I can be creative and exercise my expertise

SKILLS

- Object Oriented Programming
- Database Architecture
- Test Driven Development
- **O** C#
- XALA O
- Java
- jQuery
- Ruby on Rails Handlebars
- O mySQL
- HTML5
- TSQL
- CSS3
- PostgreSQL
- Bootstrap
- MongoDB
- Illustrator
- JavaScript
- Photoshop
- Node.js
- InDesign
- Express.js
- Corel Draw
- AngularJS
- Revit

EXPERIENCE



Web Development Immersive at General Assembly

Jun 20115- Sept 2015 | Boston, US

As a software engineer I had already some software development experience. The projects that I had worked on were not web based and I have been eager to bridge that gap in my professional growth. Joining GA's WDI allowed me to get hands-on full time web experience. I got to learn *Ruby on Rails, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, AngularJS, Handlebars, PostgreSQL, MongoDB.*



Software Developer at Nemetschek Bulgaria

Jun 2011 - Mar 2013 | Sofia, Bulgaria

As part of the international .NET development team, I worked on application used for **3D visualization** and data exchange of architectural/contractual elements. I participated in requirement discussions, prototyping sessions and software architectural planning. I designed and developed algorithms and user interfaces using **C# 3.5.** The tools used in the development process included **Visual Studio 2008**, **MS SQL Server** and **Perfoce**.



Marketing And Advertising Manager at PROFILINK Ltd

Oct 2007 - Apr 2011 | Plovdiv, Bulgaria

In a larger scale production company I started as a advertising specialist and my responsibilities were limited only to *assuring best quality* of collateral and media presence. With time and hard work I grew into a department manager. I had to *establish effective working relations* with contractors and advertising agencies and to ensure best presence of the company on the market. lorganized and managed company events. The part I loved the most was working in a team.



Prepress And Design Specialist at Impress Bulgaria

Jun 2006 - Aug 2007 | Plovdiv, Bulgaria

My main responsibility in a small print company was to prepare advertising materials for the printing machines. Those varied from business cards, full-sized product catalogs, to product packaging and corporate vehicle branding. I used *Adobe InDesign, Photoshop, Illustrator, Acrobat, Corel Draw and company-specific software* to keep track of work orders. I worked with clients on a daily basis to meet their visual design expectations and help them achieve their goals.

EDUCATION



MS in Software Technologies

2006 - 2008 | Plovdiv, Bulgaria



BS in Computer Science 2002 - 2006 | Plovdiv, Bulgaria